http://www.aisgroup.com/privacy-policy

Independent thinkingfor global investing
Adapting to global change through rigorous, independent investment analysis
Privacy Policy
AIS Capital Management, L.P., has always strived to maintain the highest standards of confidentiality and to respect the privacy of our investors. Accordingly, we are providing this Privacy Notice to investors who apply for or obtain financial products and services from us.
This Privacy Notice sets forth our policies with respect to nonpublic personal information of individual investors and prospective investors (“Investors”).
Information We Collect About You. We collect nonpublic personal information about Investors primarily from the information we receive in subscription documents or other forms submitted to us. We may also collect information from Investor transactions with us and/or our affiliates.
Disclosure Policies. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our Investors or former investors to anyone, other than to our affiliates, and except as permitted by law, such as information that we provide to prime brokers and our outside accountants and attorneys in order to service your investment with the Partnership (collectively, “Service Providers”).
Information Safeguarding Policy. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about Investors to those of our employees and our Service Providers who utilize the information to enable us to provide our services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic information.
IF OUR RELATIONSHIP ENDS, WE WILL CONTINUE TO TREAT THE INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY NOTICE.
